(Sheldon:)Have a seat.
We'll get started with the interview.
(Raj:)You're kidding.
(Prof Laughlin:)Please.
(Howard:)All right.
[RAJ SIGHS]
(Sheldon:)So....
(Sheldon:)That's what you wear to an interview?
Come on, we've been friends for years.
(Sheldon:)Oh, pulling strings, are we?
(Raj:)Sheldon, for God's sakes,
don't make me beg.
Buzzinga.
(Sheldon:)You've fallen victim to another one
of my classic practical jokes.
(Sheldon:)I'm your boss now.
You may wanna laugh at that.
Ah. This is nice,
having the place to ourselves, isn't it?
(Leonard:)Uh-huh.
(Leonard:)Now that Raj is working for Sheldon,
I don't have to chauffeur him around.
(Leonard:)Plus, yeah, with them working late
so much, we get some privacy.
PENNY:
Mm-hm.